rollanet.org 2019-08-03

# RollaNet InfoCenter - RollaNet Privacy Policy

* * *

|  |    

* * *

**RollaNet Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to the entire RollaNet website, and all RollaNet Services, including but not limited to RollaNet Memberships, Classifieds, Business & Organization Directory, and any other services provided by RollaNet.

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy of our visitors is important to us. 

At RollaNet.org, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit RollaNet.org, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. if you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us. 

Log Files 

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox or Chrome), the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons 

RollaNet.org uses cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include recording favorite ads you have selected in our Classifieds, or the ability to login to some of our features. 

We also use third party advertisements on RollaNet.org to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Missouri real estate ads to someone in Missouri, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

DoubleClick DART Cookie 

\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on RollaNet.org based on a users prior visits to our site.   
\- Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to RollaNet.org and other sites on the Internet.   
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). 

Our Advertising Partners 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
\- [Google](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)  
\- [Chitika](http://www.chitika.net/privacy)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on RollaNet.org and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site. RollaNet.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

Third Party Privacy Policies 

You should consult the respective privacy policies (linked above) of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. RollaNet.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

Children's Information 

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. RollaNet.org does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that RollaNet.org has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records. 

Online Privacy Policy Only 

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. 

Consent 

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms. 

Update 

Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Thursday, October 8th, 2015. 

|  |
